<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/joeseoj/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/joeseoj/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-28T11:13:55-05:00</updated><id>/joeseoj/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Non-Breaking Space</title><subtitle>A place to post things I make, things I'm thinking about, and other things.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Blaze Orange</title><link href="/joeseoj/poetry/2021/04/23/blaze-orange.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blaze Orange" /><published>2021-04-23T20:48:11-05:00</published><updated>2021-04-23T20:48:11-05:00</updated><id>/joeseoj/poetry/2021/04/23/blaze-orange</id><content type="html" xml:base="/joeseoj/poetry/2021/04/23/blaze-orange.html">&lt;p&gt;To fetch a twitching bird drizzling blood and kicking&lt;br /&gt; 
gravel but not really snow, hard slush and mud,&lt;br /&gt;
hunters roll by slowly, orange blazing.&lt;br /&gt;
The dusk and cold deepen as the sun sets, carrying&lt;br /&gt;
a picture of me as a child with my address on its back.&lt;br /&gt;
Not even ice that I made up frozen, but water&lt;br /&gt;
clear and cold, whispering in dim culverts and&lt;br /&gt;
in the woods, staying out of the light.&lt;br /&gt;
I lie.&lt;br /&gt;
But and only because my foul smell catches them.&lt;br /&gt;
A pervert at the county fair took that picture when I was 12.&lt;br /&gt;
Now I’m loose as thread thrown into bed and starlings&lt;br /&gt;
break from the wires overhead.&lt;br /&gt;
Boots bloody, I am snow lying in the ditches.&lt;br /&gt;
I am not frozen.&lt;br /&gt;
Only because my lying offends them.&lt;br /&gt;
The hunters are young and I whisper to them, hiding&lt;br /&gt;
in long shadows of trunks and limbs as they&lt;br /&gt;
hop the barbed wire with the guns.&lt;br /&gt;
He stomps back through the sedge, and then he is off,&lt;br /&gt;
tossing the flecked grouse.&lt;br /&gt;
And only because the muddy water running under me&lt;br /&gt;
in the ditch in the orange dusk, road hunting&lt;br /&gt;
for grouse, the noise of it running through my fingers,&lt;br /&gt;
keeps them awake.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">To fetch a twitching bird drizzling blood and kicking gravel but not really snow, hard slush and mud, hunters roll by slowly, orange blazing. The dusk and cold deepen as the sun sets, carrying a picture of me as a child with my address on its back. Not even ice that I made up frozen, but water clear and cold, whispering in dim culverts and in the woods, staying out of the light. I lie. But and only because my foul smell catches them. A pervert at the county fair took that picture when I was 12. Now I’m loose as thread thrown into bed and starlings break from the wires overhead. Boots bloody, I am snow lying in the ditches. I am not frozen. Only because my lying offends them. The hunters are young and I whisper to them, hiding in long shadows of trunks and limbs as they hop the barbed wire with the guns. He stomps back through the sedge, and then he is off, tossing the flecked grouse. And only because the muddy water running under me in the ditch in the orange dusk, road hunting for grouse, the noise of it running through my fingers, keeps them awake.</summary></entry></feed>